https://conservastore.com//privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Conserv-A-Store
Skip to Main Content
Search for:
$0.00
Login / Register
In your yard, got a long run  where you need sturdy edging MEGA Edge Border will do it!
Shop by Room
Bathroom
Kitchen
Outside Gardening
Save WaterSave Water Eco Friendly Water Saving Products that take No Brain Power Conserv-A-Store wants you to Save Water any way you can. We offer a great selection of water saving products, water saving devices, and water saving kits for your bathroom, kitchen, home, & office. We have a wide selection of low flow shower head, .35 and .5 gpm faucet aerators, lowest flow HET 1.0 gpf water saving toilets. High Efficiency Watersense Toilets can be a simple and modern change that takes little effort but makes a big impact in your remodeled bathroom. A new water saving shower head can add that daily shower a place of peace and even give you more extended showers since the best water saving technique is to have shorter showers; kill two birds with one stone by getting a low flow shower head. We also have a large selection of water saving kits for the Green Beginner to the long time Green Pro. We even have the hands free faucet called the most innovative kitchen addition, the Tapmaster. Shop with us for all your water saving needs and we encourage you to share your water and sewer usage amounts with us so we can…
Tapmasters
All Products
Water Saving Kits
Hands Free Faucet
Low Flow Shower Heads
Low Flow Faucets
Low Flow Aerators
Low Flow Toilets
Water Saving Solutions
Eco Friendly LifeEco Friendly Life Turn Your Entire Life Green without Sacrificing Anything Numerous things can be categorized as sustainable. Things that recycle, reuse, conserve, or save a particular resource or item can all be called sustainable. We have to recognise the things we use in our everyday life that can be reused, recycled, or even use less of. In this category you will find products that are recycled into new products life our Rubber Mulch products that are made from recycled tires as well as many other products we feature that can help you conserve energy, water, and the planet’s natural resources. We encourage you to add or begin the trend for those around you who do not think conserving is easy or not knowledgeable about how to go green. No matter where you are in the journey of going green by having a eco life, we have the product for you. Should you need any help in your shopping process feel free to reach out to us and we’ll be glad to help.
Recycled Rubber Tree Rings & Mulch Mats
Eco Friendly Gardening
Eco Friendly Home
Everyday Green Information And Resources
General Products
Informational Links
Tree Ring Mulch Mats Made of Recycled Goods
Recycled Rubber Mulch Mats
Rubber Mulch Tree Rings and Mulch Mats
Conserve EnergyConserv-A-Store offers a broad selection of Energy Saving products from 20000 hr long life incandescent light bulbs, 9000 hr chandelier bulbs and of course LED bulbs with up to 50000 hr life. We offer light bulb switches, light bulb timers and controls, that will help you lower your electricity bill and save you money. We offer Electricity and Energy Saving Kits for those wanting to be Green or Greener. Weatherization protection can save you a lot of money and we have the tools to make this happen. HVAC wall thermostats are a natural for correct hvac control-we have a good array for you. Come to Conserv-A-Store to save Energy
Long Lasting Light Bulbs
Energy Saving Kits
Weatherization
Energy Saving Information And Resources
Electrical Energy Saving Products
Long Life and Long Lasting Incandescent and LED Light Bulbs
Solar Energy ProductsConserv-A-Store’s Solar Energy Products Category is for you to go solar in a small or large way. We have solar experts available to design any residential or light commercial Solar Power System you want
Solar Sign Lighting
Solar Energy Information And Resources
American Solar Energy Society
Solar Power is NOT Dead…
Wind Power Monthly
Our Blog
Privacy Policy
Conserv-A-Store Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
Do we use "cookies"?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Chrome or Safari) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Conserv-A-Store, Inc. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?
To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.
To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.
Third party links
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).
Changes to our policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on December 14, 2019
Questions and feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. We are a small company and hire only the best associates so we all have private lives and we try to treat you the way we'd want to be treated
Online Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
CUSTOMER SERVICE
Help/FAQ
Privacy Policy
About Us
Terms + Conditions
JOIN OUR MAILING LIST
Email*
CONTACT US
(407) 898-2284
Email Us
Store Hours:
Monday-Sunday | 8am-8pm EST USA
Developed by Penner Web Design | ©2020
My Cart
My Account
Conserv-A-Store|The Green Solution for Your Life
Deal Of The Day
All Products
Shop by Room
Bathroom
Outside Gardening
Kitchen
Save WaterSave Water Eco Friendly Water Saving Products that take No Brain Power Conserv-A-Store wants you to Save Water any way you can. We offer a great selection of water saving products, water saving devices, and water saving kits for your bathroom, kitchen, home, & office. We have a wide selection of low flow shower head, .35 and .5 gpm faucet aerators, lowest flow HET 1.0 gpf water saving toilets. High Efficiency Watersense Toilets can be a simple and modern change that takes little effort but makes a big impact in your remodeled bathroom. A new water saving shower head can add that daily shower a place of peace and even give you more extended showers since the best water saving technique is to have shorter showers; kill two birds with one stone by getting a low flow shower head. We also have a large selection of water saving kits for the Green Beginner to the long time Green Pro. We even have the hands free faucet called the most innovative kitchen addition, the Tapmaster. Shop with us for all your water saving needs and we encourage you to share your water and sewer usage amounts with us so we can…
Tapmasters
All Products
Grey Water Recycling Systems
Hands Free Faucet
Low Flow Aerators
Low Flow Faucets
Low Flow Shower Heads
Low Flow Toilets
More Water Saving Products
Rainwater Harvesting System
Water Saving Solutions
Solar Thermal Heating Questionnaire
Water Saving Lowest Flow Faucet Aerators
Water Saving Products
Eco Friendly LifeEco Friendly Life Turn Your Entire Life Green without Sacrificing Anything Numerous things can be categorized as sustainable. Things that recycle, reuse, conserve, or save a particular resource or item can all be called sustainable. We have to recognise the things we use in our everyday life that can be reused, recycled, or even use less of. In this category you will find products that are recycled into new products life our Rubber Mulch products that are made from recycled tires as well as many other products we feature that can help you conserve energy, water, and the planet’s natural resources. We encourage you to add or begin the trend for those around you who do not think conserving is easy or not knowledgeable about how to go green. No matter where you are in the journey of going green by having a eco life, we have the product for you. Should you need any help in your shopping process feel free to reach out to us and we’ll be glad to help.
Eco Friendly Gardening
Eco Friendly Home
Everyday Green Information and Resources
Recycled Rubber Mulch Mats
Recycled Rubber Tree Rings & Mulch Mats
Tree Ring Mulch Mats Made of Recycled Goods
Informational Links
General Products
Conserve EnergyConserv-A-Store offers a broad selection of Energy Saving products from 20000 hr long life incandescent light bulbs, 9000 hr chandelier bulbs and of course LED bulbs with up to 50000 hr life. We offer light bulb switches, light bulb timers and controls, that will help you lower your electricity bill and save you money. We offer Electricity and Energy Saving Kits for those wanting to be Green or Greener. Weatherization protection can save you a lot of money and we have the tools to make this happen. HVAC wall thermostats are a natural for correct hvac control-we have a good array for you. Come to Conserv-A-Store to save Energy
Long Lasting Light Bulbs
Energy Saving Kits
Weatherization
Long Life and Long Lasting Incandescent and LED Light Bulbs
Electrical Energy Saving Products
Solar Energy ProductsConserv-A-Store’s Solar Energy Products Category is for you to go solar in a small or large way. We have solar experts available to design any residential or light commercial Solar Power System you want
Solar Sign Lighting
American Solar Energy Society
Solar Power is NOT Dead…
Wind Power Monthly
Blog
Yes, We Offer GREAT GREEN PRODUCTS, but We Also Have Extensive Knowledge and Creativity and We Want You Satisfied with Your Experience
Do you have any questions?
